http://www.sterlingvans.com/privacy

Privacy Policy
Your privacy is important to Sterling Vans.
This privacy statement provides information about the personal information that Sterling Vans collects, and the ways in which Sterling Vans uses that personal information.
Personal Information Collection
Sterling Vans may collect and use the following kinds of personal information:
information about your use of this website (including pages visited, time on each page, etc.)
information that you provide using for the purpose of registering with the website (including name, email, phone number)
information about transactions carried out over this website (including billing address, shipping address, phone number, etc.)
information that you provide for the purpose of subscribing to the website services (including email address, phone number, address, etc.)
any other information that you send to Sterling Vans.
Using Personal Information
Sterling Vans may use your personal information to:
administer this website
personalize the website for you
enable your access to and use of the website services
publish information about you on the website
send to you products that you purchase
supply to you services that you purchase
send you statements and invoices
collect payments from you
send you marketing communications.
Where Sterling Vans discloses your personal information to its agents or sub-contractors for these purposes, the agent or sub-contractor in question will be obligated to use that personal information in accordance with the terms of this privacy statement.
In addition to the disclosures reasonably necessary for the purposes identified elsewhere above, Sterling Vans may disclose your personal information to the extent that it is required to do so by law, in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings, and in order to establish, exercise or defend its legal rights.
Securing Your Data
Sterling Vans will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.
Sterling Vans will store all the personal information you provide on its secure servers.
Information relating to electronic transactions entered into via this website will be
protected by encryption technology.
Cross-Border Data Transfers
Information that Sterling Vans collects may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which Sterling Vans operates to enable the use of the information in accordance with this privacy policy.
In addition, personal information that you submit for publication on the website will be published on the internet and may be available around the world.
You agree to such cross-border transfers of personal information.
Updating This Statement
Sterling Vans may update this privacy policy by posting a new version on this website.
You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are familiar with any changes.
Other Websites
This website contains links to other websites.
Sterling Vans is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of any third party.
Contact Sterling Vans
If you have any questions about this privacy policy or Sterling Vans's treatment of your personal information, please write to:
by email to vanguy566@aol.com
This privacy statement is based on a Freenetlaw template supplied by Employment Law Contracts.
PLEASE RETAIN THIS CREDIT AND THESE LINKS IN ACCORDANCE WITH THE TERMS OF THE CREATIVE COMMONS ATTRIBUTION LICENSE UNDER WHICH THE TEMPLATE IS PROVIDED.
Sterling Van Sales
Long Island, New York
Call us at 516-398-6473
Appointments Available
Monday thru Friday
10:00 a.m. to 8:00 p.m.
Saturday & Sunday
11:00 a.m. to 4:00 p.m.
Luxury for Less
Sterling Van Sales has the largest inventory selection of new conversion vans in the entire Northeast including New York, New Jersey, Pennsylvania, Connecticut, Vermont, Massachusetts, New Hampshire and Maine.
Testimonials
"Van sold! I am impressed. I have been selling vehicles and things on major selling websites, but nothing compares to the leads I received for my van, and the quick sale from Sterling Vans. Harry and the team here are committed to a great site, great response and to the customer. Thank you!"
-Sam V.
We Want Your Van
Sterling Van Sales has the largest inventory selection available in the Tri-State area. Call us today and start enjoying your travel time in a new or used conversion van.
Check Us Out
We Offer Only Premium Van Conversions on Chevy, GMC and Ford
Social
FAQ
SITEMAP
LINKS
TERMS OF USE
PRIVACY POLICY
STERLING VANS is expanding!!!! Vans now available in the Albany, Syracuse, Rochester, and Buffalo areas. We also are expanding to the states of Connecticut, Massachusetts, Vermont and New Hampshire! Conversion vans are in stock and ready for immediate delivery.
Interested in a Conversion van and looking for the best priced vans? Look no further! Sterling Van Sales has the used conversion van for you. Cargo vans, Church vans, dog show vans, travel vans, and every day vans. We have both high top vans and low top conversion vans. We carry full size vans and mini vans, work and play vans. We also sell lease return vans at great prices! We have such a large selection of vans, you won't need to look anywhere else!
Features, specifications and optional equipment and all other information is subject to change without notice.
